[{"item":0,"type":"question","question":"Is it a mammal?","yes":1,"no":2},
{"item":1,"type":"question","question":"Does it live in the sea?","yes":3,"no":4},
{"item":16,"type":"answer","answer":"Turtle"},
{"item":12,"type":"answer","answer":"Dolphin"},
{"item":18,"type":"answer","answer":"Lion"},
{"item":5,"type":"answer","answer":"Narwhal"},
{"item":3,"type":"question","question":"Does it have a horn?","no":6,"yes":5},
{"item":14,"type":"answer","answer":"Dog"},
{"item":4,"type":"question","question":"Is it domesticated?","no":8,"yes":7},
{"item":9,"type":"answer","answer":"Seal"},
{"item":6,"type":"question","question":"Does it have whiskers?","no":10,"yes":9},
{"item":11,"type":"answer","answer":"Whale"},
{"item":10,"type":"question","question":"Is it huge?","no":12,"yes":11},
{"item":13,"type":"answer","answer":"Cat"},
{"item":7,"type":"question","question":"Does it always land on its feet?","no":14,"yes":13},
{"item":15,"type":"answer","answer":"Mosquito"},
{"item":2,"type":"question","question":"Is it a bug?","no":16,"yes":15},
{"item":20,"type":"answer","answer":"Deer"},
{"item":8,"type":"question","question":"Is it a predator?","no":17,"yes":18},
{"item":19,"type":"answer","answer":"Zebra"},
{"item":17,"type":"question","question":"Is it black and white?","no":20,"yes":19}]